{
    "id": "4af909dd32b2467ba65fc50961802a46",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... Tokyo last summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "See that the patient ...................................... complete rest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "has",
                "is having"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................  for his reply for two weeks now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am waiting",
                "have been waiting",
                "was waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ......................................... to college to meet the principal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother ............................................ tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would arrive",
                "is arriving",
                "will have arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The train ...................................... by the time we reach the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "would leave",
                "will have left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When I saw him he ........................................ writing a letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Every morning I .......................................... the paper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "will read",
                "would read"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you when the guests ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Heat ...................................... and cold .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expand, contract",
                "expands, contracts",
                "is expanding, is contracting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}